<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>Restored Monsters Pack: Judgement Free</name>
    <directory>restoredmonsterspackjudgementfree</directory>
    <id></id>
    <description>This is an alternate version of [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3239551710]Restored Monsters Pack[/url] that includes any content removed from the original due to overlap with [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3343815332]Last Judgement[/url].

[b][u]Do not enable this mod alongside Restored Monsters Pack or Last Judgement or else it will cause issues![/u][/b]

[h2]FAQ[/h2]

[b]Why not include these enemies in the original mod?[/b]
With Last Judgement being the definitive cut content experience, we try to make it so the Restored Mods don't have any content overlap with the mod at all. Most content in Last Judgement is significantly different than what Restored Mods has despite both building off the same concepts, with LJ usually diverging from the original design while RM is more faithful to how it was in Antibirth. However, there are some cases in which Last Judgement implements content already in Restored Monsters 1 to 1. Since LJ has more of a creative right to use this content than us, we have opted to remove features from Restored Mods if we feel that LJ has done a better job at implementing it.

However, we have seen some users requesting that we put whatever we remove from Restored Monsters into a seperate mod so that it can be enjoyed if you do not want to use REPENTOGON+ or Last Judgement.

[b]What is the difference between this mod and Restored Monsters?[/b]
Both mods are near identical, with the "Judgement Free" edition including 3 enemies that already exist in Last Judgement. This list will expand once Last Judgement gets updated for the final time. When this update does come out, any content in RM that we feel is too similar to anything in this LJ update will be removed from the main mod and moved here.

[b]Does this mod require REPENTOGON+?[/b]
This mod does not require REPENTOGON+, but it is recommended for a better, bug free experience.

[h2]Works with Repentance+![/h2] 

[h2]Contributors[/h2] 
We Strvn, Sillst, Redstinger, Pandora, InfiniteCosmos, Kittenchilly, Mr. R, Kerkel, vor_kakisha, Acexolotl, Goganidze, Michael8587, Watchmeojo, Skelej64, Lesser_Star, ENFOR, PixelPls, Lazarus, Firework, Brakedude, Orange Ice Pop, Reixen, steve2552, Pinchalin, TheReturnofGarnk, and JaRo7126.


[h2]Special thanks to[/h2] 
[code][u]Public Entertainment Networked Interactive Software[/u] - For the original Antibirth mod as well as the content and concepts that this mod builds off of[/code]
 

[h2]Restored Hub Discord Link[h2]
https://discord.gg/BYGmAhgG8k

</description>
    <version>1.0</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Rooms"/>
    <tag id="Floors"/>
    <tag id="Enemies"/>
    <tag id="Hazards"/>
    <tag id="Graphics"/>
</metadata>
